Guide to the Yale Course Lectures Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Yale lectures, 1720-1980; Accession 19ND-A-394
  - Bacon, Leonard., 1843 (Box 29, Folder 144)
    Notetaker: Barnum, Samuel W. (1841 Yale College)
  - Fitch, Eleazar T., 1843 (Box 29, Folder 144)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A., 1843 (Box 29, Folder 144)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1843 (Box 29, Folder 144)
  - Unknown., 1895-98 (Box 30, Folder 145)
    Notetaker: Symington, W. Clark. (1902 Sheffield)
    Subject: Botany
  - Unknown., 1895-98 (Box 30, Folder 145)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., undated (Box 30, Folder 146)
    Notetaker: MacWhorter, Alexander. (1842 Yale College)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1843-44 (Box 30, Folder 147)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1844 (Box 30, Folder 147A)
  - Fitch, Eleazar T., 1837-42 (Box 31, Folder 148)
    Notetaker: Ely, William D. (1836 Yale College)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A., 1837-42 (Box 31, Folder 148)
    Notetaker: Stoddard, David T. (1838 Yale College)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1837-42 (Box 31, Folder 148)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1838 (Box 31, Folder 149)
    Notetaker: Dutton, S. W. S. (1833 Yale College)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A., 1843-44 (Box 31, Folder 150)
  - Olmsted, Denison., 1838 (Box 31, Folder 150)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1842 (Box 31, Folder 150)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A., 1844 (Box 31, Folder 151)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1842 (Box 31, Folder 151)
  - Fitch, Eleazar T., undated (Box 31, Folder 152)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., undated (Box 31, Folder 152)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1840 (Box 32, Folder 153)
    Notetaker: McHarg, W. N.
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1838 (Box 32, Folder 154)
    Notetaker: Saxton, J. A.
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1838 (Box 32, Folder 154)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1838 (Box 32, Folder 155)
  - Fitch, Eleazar T., 1836-37 (Box 33, Folder 156)
    Notetaker: Porter, Samuel. (1829 Yale College)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1836-37 (Box 33, Folder 156)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1840 (Box 33, Folder 157)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., undated (Box 33, Folder 158)
  - Unknown., undated (Box 33, Folder 159)
    Notetaker: Tracy, Howard C. (1887 Yale College)
  - Unknown., 1838-39 (Box 34, Folder 160)
    Notetaker: Trumbull, James Hammond. (1842 Yale College)
  - Unknown., 1839 (Box 34, Folder 160)
  - Peck, Epaphroditus., 1903-04 (Box 34, Folder 161)
    Notetaker: Peck, Epaphroditus.
  - Peck, Epaphroditus., 1904 (Box 34, Folder 162)
  - Peck, Epaphroditus., 1903-04 (Box 34, Folder 163)
  - Peck, Epaphroditus., 1904-05 (Box 34, Folder 164)
  - Peck, Epaphroditus., 1906-09 (Box 34, Folder 165)
  - Granville, William A., 1900-01 (Box 35, Folder 166)
    Notetaker: Granville, William A.
  - Granville, William A., 1901-02 (Box 35, Folder 167)
  - Granville, William A., 1903-04 (Box 35, Folder 168)
  - Granville, William A., 1905-06 (Box 35, Folder 169)
  - Smith, P. F.[?]., 1903-04 (Box 36, Folder 170)
    Notetaker: Dodd, Edward L.[?]. (1902 Graduate School)
  - Dwight, Timothy, Younger., 1863 (Box 36, Folder 171)
    Notetaker: Chamberlain, Leander T. (1863 Yale College)
  - Fisher, George P., 1863 (Box 36, Folder 171)
  - Woolsey, Theodore Dwight., 1863 (Box 36, Folder 171)
    Subject: Political Science
  - Hedrick, Earle R., 1901-02 (Box 36, Folder 172)
    Notetaker: Hedrick, Earle R.
  - Hedrick, Earle R., undated (Box 37, Folder 173)
  - Hedrick, Earle R., undated (Box 37, Folder 174)
  - Hedrick, Earle R., 1901-02 (Box 38, Folder 175)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 39, Folder 176)
    Notetaker: Heermance, Theodore W.
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 39, Folder 177)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 39, Folder 178)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 39, Folder 179)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 39, Folder 180)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 39, Folder 181)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 39, Folder 182)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 39, Folder 183)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 39, Folder 184)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 39, Folder 185)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 39, Folder 186)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 39, Folder 187)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 188)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 189)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 190)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 191)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 192)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 193)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 194)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 195)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 196)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 197)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 198)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 199)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 201)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 202)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 203)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 204)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 205)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 206)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 207)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 208)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., 1903-04 (Box 40, Folder 209)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., 1903-04 (Box 40, Folder 210)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., 1903-04 (Box 40, Folder 211)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 40, Folder 212)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., 1903-04 (Box 41, Folder 213)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 41, Folder 214)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., 1903 (Box 41, Folder 215)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., 1903 (Box 41, Folder 216)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., 1904 (Box 41, Folder 217)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 41, Folder 218)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 41, Folder 219)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 41, Folder 220)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 41, Folder 221)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., 1903-04 (Box 41, Folder 222)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., 1903-04 (Box 41, Folder 223)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 41, Folder 224)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 41, Folder 225)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 41, Folder 226)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 41, Folder 227)
  - Heermance, Theodore W., undated (Box 41, Folder 228)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1819-20 (Box 42, Folder 229)
    Subject: Medicine
  - Ives, Eli., 1820 circa (Box 42, Folder 230)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1820 circa (Box 42, Folder 230)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1825 (Box 42, Folder 231)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1825 (Box 42, Folder 232)
  - Ives, Eli., 1830 (Box 42, Folder 233)
  - Bartlett., 1832 (Box 42, Folder 234)
  - Clark., 1832 (Box 42, Folder 234)
  - Gilman., 1832 (Box 42, Folder 234)
  - Parker., 1832 (Box 42, Folder 234)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1832 (Box 42, Folder 234)
  - Torrey., 1832 (Box 42, Folder 234)
  - Watts., 1832 (Box 42, Folder 234)
  - Ives, Eli., 1840 (Box 42, Folder 235)
  - Hooker, Worthington., 1856-57 (Box 43, Folder 236)
  - Knight, Jonathan., 1856-57 (Box 43, Folder 236)
  - Knight, Jonathan., 1858-59 (Box 43, Folder 237)
  - Unknown., 1836-37 (Box 43, Folder 238)
    Notetaker: Baldwin, Nathan C. (1837 M.D.)
    Subject: Medicine?
  - Ives, Eli., 1836circa (Box 43, Folder 239)
  - Tully, William., 1836-37 (Box 43, Folder 240)
  - Tully, William., 1836 (Box 43, Folder 241)
  - Unknown., 1906-07 (Box 43, Folder 242)
    Notetaker: Barbour, Henry Gray.
  - Unknown., 1886 (Box 44, Folder 243)
    Notetaker: Beach, Edward C. (1888 M.D.)
  - Unknown., 1886-87 (Box 44, Folder 244)
  - Unknown., 1887 (Box 44, Folder 245)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1823-24 (Box 44, Folder 246)
    Notetaker: Bedford, Andrew.
  - Ives, Eli., 1814 (Box 44, Folder 247)
    Notetaker: Bissell, Asaph L. (1815 M.D.)
  - Ives, Eli., 1830-31 (Box 44, Folder 248)
    Notetaker: Burritt, Anthony B. (1832 M.D.)
  - Winternitz, Milton C., 1927-28 (Box 45, Folder 249)
    Notetaker: Carbon, Earl R. (1931 M.D.)
  - Unknown., 1929-1930 (Box 45, Folder 250)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1813 (Box 45, Folder 251)
    Notetaker: Carpenter, Elijah W.
  - Smith, Nathan., 1813-14 (Box 45, Folder 252)
  - Ives, Eli., 1813-14 (Box 45, Folder 253)
  - Ives, Eli., 1813-14 (Box 46, Folder 254)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1814 (Box 46, Folder 255)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1814 (Box 46, Folder 256)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1814 (Box 46, Folder 257)
  - Tully, William., undated (Box 46, Folder 258)
    Notetaker: Clarke, Samuel F. (1837 M.D.)
  - Ives, Eli., 1840 (Box 46, Folder 259)
    Notetaker: Daggett, David L. (1839 Yale College)
  - Hubbard, Thomas., 1829-30 (Box 46, Folder 260)
    Notetaker: Downs, Myron. (1830 M.D.)
  - Tully, William., 1829-30 (Box 46, Folder 260)
  - Unknown., 1888circa (Box 47, Folder 261)
    Notetaker: Ferris, H. B. (1890 M.D.)
  - Ives, Eli., 1825 (Box 47, Folder 262)
    Notetaker: Fields, Edward. (1829 M.D.)
  - Hubbard, Stephen G., 1873-74 (Box 47, Folder 263)
    Notetaker: Fitch, Charles W. (1874 M.D.)
  - Smith, David P., 1873-1874 (Box 47, Folder 263)
  - White, Moses C., 1873-1874 (Box 47, Folder 264)
  - Hubbard, Stephen G., 1874 (Box 47, Folder 264)
  - Smith, David P., 1874 (Box 47, Folder 264)
  - White, Moses C., 1874 (Box 47, Folder 264)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1824 (Box 48, Folder 265)
    Notetaker: Fitch, Worham L.
  - Smith, Nathan., 1825 (Box 48, Folder 266)
  - Ives, Eli., circa 1825 (Box 48, Folder 267)
  - Ives, Eli., 1828 (Box 49, Folder 268)
    Notetaker: Gillette, Horace C. (1829 M.D.)
  - Ives, Eli., 1828 (Box 49, Folder 269)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1828 (Box 49, Folder 270)
  - Ives, Eli., 1827-1828 (Box 49, Folder 271)
    Notetaker: Grosvenor, William.
  - Knight, Jonathan., 1827-28 (Box 49, Folder 271)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1827-1828 (Box 49, Folder 271)
  - Hussey, Raymond., 1926-1929 (Box 50, Folder 272)
    Notetaker: Hahn, T. F., Jr. (1931 M.D.)
  - Rettger, Leo F., 1926-29 (Box 50, Folder 272)
    Notetaker: Hahn, T.F., Jr. (1931 M.D.)
  - Smith [George H.?]., 1926-1929 (Box 50, Folder 272)
  - Winternitz, Milton C., 1926-1929 (Box 50, Folder 272)
  - Hussey, Raymond., 1929 (Box 50, Folder 273)
  - Winternitz, Milton C., 1929 (Box 50, Folder 273)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1818-19 (Box 50, Folder 274)
    Notetaker: Hall, David E. (1820 M.D.)
  - Knight, Jonathan., 1828-29? (Box 50, Folder 275)
    Notetaker: Hubbard, Denison H. (1829 M.D.)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1821 (Box 50, Folder 276)
    Notetaker: Humphrey, Phelps.
  - Ives, Eli., 1837circa (Box 50, Folder 277)
    Notetaker: Hungerford, A.M.? (1839 M.D.)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1818-19 (Box 51, Folder 278)
    Notetaker: Hunt, Orrin.
  - Smith, Nathan., 1814 (Box 51, Folder 279)
    Notetaker: Lay, Willoughby Lynde. (1816 M.D.)
  - Ives, Eli., 1833-35 (Box 51, Folder 280)
    Notetaker: Mathewson, Rufus Wellington.
  - McClellan., 1833-1835 (Box 51, Folder 280)
  - Tully, William., 1833-1835 (Box 51, Folder 280)
  - Woodward., 1833-1835 (Box 51, Folder 280)
  - Ives, Eli., 1824 (Box 51, Folder 281)
    Notetaker: Moses, Hiram?. (1825 M.D.)
  - Ives, Eli., 1827-1828 (Box 52, Folder 282)
    Notetaker: Newcomb, John E. (1829 M.D.)
  - Silliman, Benjamin., 1827-1830 (Box 52, Folder 283)
    Subject: Chemistry;MEDICINE
  - Ives, Eli., 1835 (Box 52, Folder 284)
    Notetaker: Platt, G. L. (1838 M.D.)
  - Ives, Eli., 1829-30 (Box 52, Folder 285)
    Notetaker: Prichard, David. (1832 M.D.)
  - Ives, Eli., 1830-31 (Box 52, Folder 286)
    Notetaker: Rockwell, William H. (1824 Yale College)
  - Knight, Jonathan., 1830-1831 (Box 52, Folder 286)
  - Knight, Jonathan., 1822-1823? (Box 53, Folder 287)
    Notetaker: Talcott, William O. (1823 M.D.)
  - Smith, Nathan., undated (Box 53, Folder 288)
  - Ives, Eli., 1822 (Box 53, Folder 289)
  - Ives, Eli., 1813 (Box 53, Folder 290)
    Notetaker: Turner, Rufus. (1830 M.D.)
  - Knight, Jonathan., 1813 (Box 53, Folder 290)
  - Silliman, Benjamin., 1813 (Box 53, Folder 290)
  - Unknown., 1886 (Box 53, Folder 291)
    Notetaker: Van Allen, Frank. (1887 M.D.)
  - Hooker, Charles., 1848-1849 (Box 53, Folder 292)
    Notetaker: Williams, William C., Jr. (1850 M.D.)
  - Knight, Jonathan., 1848-1849 (Box 53, Folder 292)
  - Smith, Nathan., 1813-1814 (Box 54, Folder 293)
    Notetaker: Woodbury, Peter P.
  - Smith, Nathan., 1813-1814 (Box 54, Folder 294)
  - Unknown., 1813 (Box 54, Folder 295)
  - Ives, Eli., 1840 (Box 55, Folder 296)
    Notetaker: Wilcoxson, Levi D. (1839 Yale College)
  - Ives, Eli., 1840 (Box 55, Folder 297)
  - Ives, Eli., 1840-41 (Box 55, Folder 298)
    Notetaker: Wilcoxson, Levi D. (1829 Yale College)
  - Ives, Eli., 1820-21 (Box 55, Folder 299)
    Notetaker: Barrett, Benjamin.
  - Ives, Eli., 1814-15 (Box 56, Folder 301)
    Notetaker: Blackman, Josiah.
  - Ives, Eli., 1826-27 (Box 56, Folder 302)
    Notetaker: Wilson, J.
  - Hubbard, Thomas., 1829 (Box 56, Folder 303)
    Notetaker: Hubbard, Thomas.
  - Hubbard, Thomas., undated (Box 56, Folder 304)
  - Knight, Jonathan., undated (Box 57, Folder 305)
    Notetaker: Lindsley, Charles A. (1852 M.D.)
  - Jewett, Pliny Adams., 1839;1849-50 (Box 57, Folder 306)
    Notetaker: Jewett, Pliny Adams.
  - Ives, Eli., 1829-30 (Box 57, Folder 307)
    Notetaker: Talcott, Alvan. (1824 Yale College)
  - Ives, Eli., 1820 (Box 57, Folder 308)
  - Ives, Eli., undated (Box 57, Folder 309)
  - Hubbard, Thomas.; Ives, Eli., undated (Box 57, Folder 310)
  - Ives, Eli.; Hubbard, Thomas., undated (Box 57, Folder 310)
  - Hubbard, Thomas; Ives, Eli., undated (Box 58, Folder 311)
  - Ives, Eli; Hubbard, Thomas., undated (Box 58, Folder 311)
  - Tully, William., undated (Box 58, Folder 312)
  - Tully, William., undated (Box 58, Folder 313)
  - Tully, William., undated (Box 58, Folder 314)
  - Tully, William., undated (Box 58, Folder 315)
  - Hubbard, Thomas., 1829? (Box 59, Folder 316)
  - Hubbard, Thomas., 1829 (Box 59, Folder 317)
  - Hubbard, Thomas., 1830 (Box 59, Folder 318)
  - Hubbard, Thomas., 1830 (Box 60, Folder 319)
  - Hubbard, Thomas., 1830 (Box 60, Folder 320)
  - Silliman, Benjamin., 1813 (Box 60, Folder 321)
    Notetaker: Hartshorn, Elijah. (1815 Yale College)
  - Mendel, Lafayette B., 1910-11 (Box 60, Folder 322)
    Notetaker: Dayton, Arthur Bliss. (1911 Sheffield)
    Subject: PHYSIOLOGY; MEDICINE?
  - Ives, Charles L., 1872-73 (Box 61, Folder 323)
    Notetaker: Newcomb, J. J. (1875 M.D.)
  - Ives, Eli., 1821 (Box 62, Folder 324)
  - Ives, Eli., 1839-40 (Box 62, Folder 325)
  - Unknown., 1814-15 (Box 62, Folder 326)
    Notetaker: Blackman, J.
  - Hubbard, Stephen G., 1874-75 (Box 63, Folder 327)
    Notetaker: Hubbard, Stephen G.
  - Hubbard, Stephen G., undated (Box 63, Folder 328)
  - Baldwin, Simeon E., 1877? (Box 63, Folder 328A)
  - Loomis, Elias., 1877? (Box 63, Folder 328A)
  - Thacher, James K. ?, 1877? (Box 63, Folder 328A)
  - Ladd, George T., 1898 (Box 64, Folder 329)
    Notetaker: Murphy, Henry Killam. (1899 Yale College)
  - Lounsbury, Thomas., 1898 (Box 64, Folder 329)
  - Scripture, Edward W., 1898 (Box 64, Folder 329)
  - Winchester, C. F. (Wesleyan)., 1898 (Box 64, Folder 329)
  - Duncan, George N., undated (Box 64, Folder 330)
  - Fisher, Irving., undated (Box 64, Folder 330)
  - Duncan, George N., 1897-98 (Box 64, Folder 331)
  - Fisher, Irving., 1897-1898 (Box 64, Folder 331)
  - Sneath, Elias H., 1897-1898 (Box 64, Folder 331)
  - Beers, Henry A., 1898 (Box 64, Folder 332)
  - Phelps, William Lyon., 1898 (Box 64, Folder 332)
  - Hadley, Arthur T., 1898 (Box 64, Folder 333)
  - Phelps, William Lyon., 1898 (Box 64, Folder 333)
  - Phelps, William Lyon., 1898 (Box 64, Folder 334)
  - Unknown., 1898 (Box 64, Folder 334)
  - Adams, George B., 1898? (Box 64, Folder 335)
  - Boardman?, 1873 (Box 65, Folder 336)
  - Silliman, Benjamin. ?, 1857-60 (Box 66, Folder 337)
    Notetaker: Colman, George W.
  - Corbin, Arthur L., 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 338)
    Notetaker: McClung, Richard G. (1939 Law)
  - Corbin, Arthur L., 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 339)
  - McDougal, Myres S., 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 340)
  - Vance, William R., 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 340)
  - McDougal, Myres S., 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 341)
  - Rogers, James G., 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 341)
  - Vance, William R., 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 341)
  - Clark, Charles E., 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 342)
  - James, Fleming., 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 342)
  - Moore, James W., 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 342)
  - James, Fleming., 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 343)
  - Shulman, Harry., 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 343)
  - Saxon, Olin G., 1935-1936 (Box 68, Folder 344)
  - Arnold, Thurman W., 1935-1936 (Box 68, Folder 345)
  - James, Fleming., 1935-1936 (Box 68, Folder 345)
  - Maggs, Douglas B., 1935-1936 (Box 68, Folder 346)
  - Unknown (Harvard?)., 1936-1937 (Box 68, Folder 347)
  - Unknown (Harvard?)., 1936-1937 (Box 68, Folder 348)
  - Unknown (Harvard?)., 1936-1937 (Box 68, Folder 349)
  - Unknown (Harvard?)., 1936-1937 (Box 68, Folder 350)
  - Unknown (Harvard?)., 1936-1937 (Box 69, Folder 351)
  - Unknown (Harvard?)., 1936-1937 (Box 69, Folder 352)
  - Unknown (Harvard?)., 1936-1937 (Box 69, Folder 353)
  - Unknown (Harvard?)., 1936-1937 (Box 69, Folder 354)
  - Unknown (Harvard?)., 1936-1937 (Box 69, Folder 355)
  - Meck, John F., 1937-1938 (Box 69, Folder 356)
  - Arnold, Thurman W., 1937-1938 (Box 69, Folder 357)
  - Dession, George H., 1937-1938 (Box 69, Folder 357)
  - Kessler, Friedrich., 1937-1938 (Box 69, Folder 358)
  - Moore, Underhill., 1937-1938 (Box 69, Folder 358)
  - Gulliver, Ashbel G., 1937-1938 (Box 70, Folder 359)
  - Gulliver, Ashbel G., 1937-1938 (Box 70, Folder 360)
  - Steffen, Roscoe T., 1937-1938 (Box 70, Folder 361)
  - Arnold, Thurman W., 1937-1938 (Box 70, Folder 362)
  - Vance, William R., 1937-1938 (Box 70, Folder 363)
  - Rostow, Eugene V., 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 364)
  - Sturges, Wesley A., 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 364)
  - Rostow, Eugene V., 1938-1939 (Box 71, Folder 365)
  - Sturges, Wesley A., 1938-1939 (Box 71, Folder 365)
  - Clark, Charles E., 1938-1939 (Box 71, Folder 366)
  - McDougal, Myres S., 1938-1939 (Box 71, Folder 366)
  - Throop, Allen E., 1938-1939 (Box 71, Folder 367)
  - Sturges, Wesley A., 1938-1939 (Box 71, Folder 368)
  - Sturges, Wesley A., 1938-1939 (Box 72, Folder 369)
  - Gulliver, Ashbel G., 1938-1939 (Box 72, Folder 370)
  - Shulman, Harry., 1938-1939 (Box 72, Folder 371)
  - Unknown., 1938-1939 (Box 72, Folder 372)
  - Dession, George H., 1938-1939 (Box 72, Folder 373)
  - Unknown., 1938-1939 (Box 72, Folder 374)
  - McClung, Richard G., 1943 (Box 72, Folder 375)
  - McClung, Richard G., 1945 (Box 72, Folder 376)
  - Wurts, John., 1900 (Box 72, Folder 377)
    Notetaker: Smith, John Thomas (1901 Law)
  - Weiss, Paul., 1963 (Box 73, Folder 378)
    Transcript
  - Weiss, Paul., 1963 (Box 73, Folder 379)
  - Weiss, Paul., audiorecording, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 380)
  - Weiss, Paul., audiorecording, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 380)
  - Unknown., undated (Box 76, Folder 381)
    Notetaker: Fritz, Emanuel (?). (1914 Forestry School)
    Subject: Forestry
  - Unknown., undated (Box 76, Folder 382)
    Notetaker: Fritz, Emanuel. (1914 Forestry School)
  - Toumey, James., 1913 (Box 76, Folder 383)
  - Levison, Jacob., 1913 (Box 76, Folder 384)
  - Graves, Arthur., 1913 (Box 76, Folder 385)
    Notetaker: Fritz, Emanuel (1914 Forestry School)
  - Coe, Wesley (?)., 1913 (Box 76, Folder 386)
  - Mason, D. T., 1914 (Box 76, Folder 387)
  - Chapman, Herman., 1912 (Box 76, Folder 388)
  - Chapman, Herman., 1913 (Box 76, Folder 389)
  - Unknown., undated (Box 76, Folder 390)
    Notetaker: Hotze, Frederick. (1899 Yale College)
  - Gassner, John., 1962-63 (Box 77, Folder 391)
  - Gassner, John., 1962-63 (Box 77, Folder 392)
  - Gassner, John., 1963 (Box 78, Folder 393)
  - Gassner, John., 1963-64 (Box 78, Folder 394)
  - Gassner, John., 1963-64 (Box 79, Folder 394)
  - Gassner, John., audiorecording, 1962-63 (Box 80, Folder 395)
  - Gassner, John., audiorecording, 1962-63 (Box 81, Folder 395)
  - Gassner, John., audiorecording, 1962-63 (Box 82, Folder 395)
  - Gassner, John., audiorecording, 1962-63 (Box 83, Folder 395)
  - Gassner, John., audiorecording, 1962-63 (Box 84, Folder 395)
  - Gassner, John., audiorecording, 1962-63 (Box 85, Folder 395)
  - Gassner, John., audiorecording, 1963-64 (Box 86, Folder 396)
  - Gassner, John., audiorecording, 1963-64 (Box 87, Folder 396)
  - Gassner, John., audiorecording, 1963-64 (Box 88, Folder 396)
  - Gassner, John., audiorecording, 1963-64 (Box 89, Folder 396)
  - Gassner, John., audiorecording, 1963-64 (Box 90, Folder 396)
  - Bemis, Samuel., 1942 (Box 91, Folder 397)
    Notetaker: Osterweis, Rollin B. (1930 Yale College)
  - Gabriel, Ralph., 1942 (Box 91, Folder 397)
  - Labaree, Leonard., 1942 (Box 91, Folder 397)
  - Potter, David., 1942 (Box 91, Folder 398)
  - Pierson, George., 1942 (Box 91, Folder 399)
  - Pierson, George., 1942 (Box 92, Folder 399)
  - Allison, John., 1943 (Box 92, Folder 400)
  - Notestein, Wallace., 1943-44 (Box 92, Folder 401)
  - Notestein, Wallace., 1942-43 (Box 92, Folder 402)
  - Holborn, Hajo., 1943 (Box 93, Folder 403)
  - Woodbine, George., 1942 (Box 93, Folder 404)
  - Allison, John., 1943 (Box 93, Folder 405)
  - Gabriel, Ralph., 1944 (Box 93, Folder 406)
  - Gabriel, Ralph., 1944-45 (Box 94, Folder 407)
  - Osterweis, Rollin B., 1943-44 (Box 94, Folder 408)
  - Osterweis, Rollin B., 1944 (Box 94, Folder 409)
    Scope and Contents note
  - Osterweis, Rollin B., circa 1940-1980 (Box 94, Folder 409)
  - Osterweis, Rollin B., circa 1940-1980 (Box 95, Folder 409)
  - Osterweis, Rollin B., circa 1940-1980 (Box 95, Folder 410)
  - Osterweis, Rollin B., 1968-1980 (Box 96, Folder 411)
  - Osterweis, Rollin B., 1952-1965 (Box 96, Folder 412)
  - Osterweis, Rollin B., 1952-1965 (Box 97, Folder 412)
  - Osterweis, Rollin B., 1969 (Box 97, Folder 413)
  - Osterweis, Rollin B., 1979-1980 (Box 97, Folder 414)
  - Packard, Lewis R., 1866 (Box 97, Folder 415)
    Notetaker: Welch, Theodore F. (1869 Yale College)
  - Mitchell, Sydney K., English Constitutional History, 1922 (Box 98, Folder 418)
    Notetaker: Dunham, William H. (1923 Yale College)
  - Taylor, Edwin C., Pictorial Art, 1922-1923 (Box 98, Folder 419A-C)
  - Dunham, William H., Chance, Coincidence, and Cacul? lecture materials, 1957-1974 (Box 99, Folder 420A-B)
  - Dunham, William H., History 21: Structure of English Civilization, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 421A-B)
  - Dunham, William H., English Constitutional History, 1967-1968 (Box 99, Folder 422)
  - Dunham, William H., History 11: Europe in the 15th and 16th Centuries -- The Secularization of Life, 1936-1938 (Box 99, Folder 423)
  - Dunham, William H., History 144a: England's Constitutional Revolution, 1529-17?, 1964-1970 (Box 100, Folder 424)
  - Dunham, William H., History of English Civilization to 1714, 1942-1943 (Box 100, Folder 425)
  - Dunham, William H., The Medieval Monarchy: 1216-1399, 1959-1967 (Box 100, Folder 426)
  - Dunham, William H., Elizabethan Accomplishment, 1939-1941 (Box 100, Folder 427)
  - Dunham, William H., Stuart Constitutions, 1603-1718, 1959-1968 (Box 100, Folder 428)
  - Dunham, William H., History 146: The Literature of English History, 1946-1949 (Box 101, Folder 429A-B)
  - Dunham, William H., Tudor Constitutionalism, 1529-1603, 1963-1967 (Box 101, Folder 430)
  - Dunham, William H., Victorian Constitution, 1956-1967 (Box 101, Folder 431)
  - Dunham, William H., Collectivist Constitution, 1950-1967 (Box 101, Folder 432)
  - Dunham, William H., Medieval Monarchy, 1399-1529, 1950-1964 (Box 101, Folder 433)
  - Dunham, William H., History 141A: Constitutional Governance in Medieval England, 1963-1970 (Box 102, Folder 434A-B)
  - Dunham, William H., History 143: Modern British Constiutionalism, 1962-1963 (Box 102, Folder 435)